McConnell, John W. Additional Arbitration Files 5961
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Arbitrations: 1982-1985 (Box 20)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - National Fuel Gas Co. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Arbitration, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - West Irondequoit Central School District and Irondequoit Educational Secretaries Arbitration, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Guilderland Central School District and Guilderland Central Teachers Association Arbitration, 1985-1987 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Guilderland Central School District and Guilderland Central Teachers Association Arbitration, 1985-1987 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Arbitrations: 1985-1987 (Box 21)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Chicago Pneumatic Tool Co. and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1985-1987 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Gates Chili Central School and Venice L. Nichols, Guidance Counselor Arbitration, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Mail Handlers Arbitration, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Schegel Corporation and Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Arbitration, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Arbitrations: 1986 (Box 22)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Rome Cable Corp. and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Arbitration, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Boise Cascade Corporation and United Paper Workers International Union Arbitration, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Arbitrations: 1986-1987 (Box 23)
  - US Postal Service Arbitrations, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Includes: arbitrations with the National Assoc. of Letter Carriers and American Postal Workers Union
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986-1990 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - City of Ithaca Fire Department and Ithaca Paid Fire Fighters Association, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Utica City School District and Utica Teachers Association Arbitration, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Utica City School District and Utica Teachers Association Arbitration, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - West Genesee School District and West Genesee Teachers Association Arbitration, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - West Genesee School District and West Genesee Teachers Association Arbitration, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Onondaga Cortland Madison BOCES and BOCES Federation of Teachers Association Arbitration, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - NYS Department of Corrections and Security Unit Employees Council 82 Arbitration, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - NYS Department of Corrections and Security Unit Employees Council 82 Arbitration, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - James River Corp. formerly Crown Zellerbach and United Paper Workers International Union Arbitration, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - James River Corp. formerly Crown Zellerbach and United Paper Workers International Union Arbitration, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Friedrich Climate Master Inc. and International Assoc. of Machinist and Aerospace Workers Arbitration, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - City of Lackawanna and Lackawanna Fire Fighters Association Arbitration, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Dunlop Tire And Rubber Corp. and Amalgamated Clothing And Textile Workers Union Arbitration, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Arbitrations: 1973, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Kendall Co. Northern Manufacturing Division and Textile Workers Union Arbitration, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Kendall Co. and United Paper Makers And Paper Workers Arbitration, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Lytron Inc. and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - American Biltrite Rubber Co, Inc. and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America Arbitration, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - WHEC, Inc. and American Federation of TV and Radio Artists Arbitration, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - City of Syracuse and Civil Service Employees Association Arbitration, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    Includes: copied photo documents
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - City of Auburn and American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees Arbitration, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - T.J. Sheehan Distributing, Inc. and Brewery Workers and Beer Distributors Arbitration, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - T.J. Sheehan Distributing, Inc. and Brewery Workers and Beer Distributors Arbitration, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Arbitrations: 1987-1988 (Box 25)
  - Auburn Police Department and American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees Arbitration, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - City of Schenectady Patrolmen's Benevolent Association Arbitration, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Service Union Arbitration, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Lipe Corporation and United Steel Workers of America Arbitration, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Lipe Corporation and United Steel Workers of American Arbitration, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Capital Newspaper Division, The Hearst Corp. and Newspaper Guild of Albany Arbitration, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Capital Newspaper Division, The Hearst Corp. and Newspaper Guild of Albany Arbitration, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Arbitrations: 1988-1990 (Box 26)
  - Utica City School District and Utica Teachers Association Arbitration, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Includes: rental agreements
  - Utica City School District and Utica Teachers Association Arbitration, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1988-1989 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1988-1989 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Packaging Corp. of America and United Paper Workers International Arbitration, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    Includes; Manufacturing and shipping charts
  - Watkins Glen Central School and Watkins Glen Faculty Association Arbitration, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Town of Henrietta, NY and Communication Workers Of America Arbitration, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Town of Henrietta, NY and Communication Workers of America Arbitration, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    Includes: floor plans/ floor lay-out
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Mail-Well Envelope Co. and International Representative ACTWU Arbitration, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Mail-Well Envelope Co. and International Representative ACTWU Arbitration, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Simmonds Precision and International of Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Arbitration, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Arbitrations: 1988-1990 (Box 27)
  - US Postal Service American Postal Service Union Arbitration, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Westmoreland Malleable Iron Co. and International Molders and Allied Workers Union Arbitration, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Includes: photo documents, and a multitude of receipts and expenses.
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    Includes: rental agreement
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - North Country Community College and North Country Community College Assoc. of Professors Arbitration, 1988-1990 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - NYS Electric and Gas State Co. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Arbitration, 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - General Foods Corporation and Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Arbitration, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - General Foods Manufacturing Corporation and Textile Workers Union Arbitration, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - General Foods Manufacturing Corporation and Textile Workers Union Arbitration, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - General Foods Manufacturing Corporation and Textile Workers Union Arbitration, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Arbitrations: 1986-1990 (Box 28)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - US Postal Service and National Association of Letter Carriers Arbitration, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - City of Auburn and American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Workers Union Arbitration, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Marcellus School District and Marcellus Faculty Association Arbitration, 1986-1988 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Marcellus School District and Marcellus Faculty Association Arbitration, 1986-1988 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - City of Rome and Rome Civil Service Employees Association Arbitration, 1989-1990 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - City of Rome and Rome Civil Service Employees Association Arbitration, 1989-1990 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Village of Baldwinsville and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees Arbitration, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Mail-Well Envelope Co. and Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Arbitration, 1987-1989 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union Arbitration, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Dundee Central School District and Dundee Teacher Association Arbitration, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Dundee Central School District and Dundee Teachers Association Arbitration, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - International Paper Co. and United Paper Workers International Union Arbitration, 1988-1989 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Linden Chemical Co. and United Steel Workers of America Arbitration, 1988-1989 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - International Paper Co. and United Paper Workers International Union Arbitration, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service and Raylene Sheets and Victory Markets, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- Arbitrations: 1989-1991 (Box 29)
  - Clinton Ditch Cooperative Co., Inc. and United Steel Workers Of America Arbitration, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Includes: Enlarged photo documents
  - Clinton's Ditch Cooperative Co., Inc. and United Steel Workers Of America Arbitration, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Agway, Inc. and American Federation of Grain Millers Local 54 Arbitration, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - City of Lackawanna and Lackawanna PBA Arbitration, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Decora and United Paper Workers International Union Arbitration, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Hoffman Air and Filtration Systems and United Steel Workers of America Arbitration, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Hoffman Air and Filtration System and United Steel Workers Of America Arbitration, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - E.I. Du Pont de Nemours and Company and Niagara Plant Employees Union Arbitration, 1990-1991 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - E.I. Du Pont de Nemours and Company and Niagara Plant Employees Union Arbitration, 1990-1991 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - E.I. Du Pont de Nemours and Company and Niagara Plant Employees Union Arbitration, 1990-1991 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Windsor Central School District and Non-Teaching Employees Of the Custodial and Transportation Staff Arbitration, 1990-1991 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Department of Correctional Service and American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees Arbitration, 1990-1991 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - C AND A Wall Coverings Inc. and United Paper Workers International Union Arbitration, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    Includes: Airline tickets and multiple receipts
  - Department of Correctional Services and American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    Arbitration with AFSCME Council 82
  - Department of Correctional Services and American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees Arbitration, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Town of Greece and Civil Service Employees Association Arbitration, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Clinton Ditch Cooperative, Inc. and United Steel Workers of America Arbitration, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Hoffman Air and Filtration Systems and United Steel Workers Of America Arbitration, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - NYS Electrical and Gas Co. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Arbitration, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Sterling Drug Co. and International Chemical Workers Union Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  micro cassette
- Sterling Drug Co. and International Chemical Workers Union Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 1)